It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Under the disgrace of being called a traitor, Musashi was about to be executed by Hanzō.
반역자라는 오명을 썼던 무사시는 한조의 손으로 처형될 처지에 놓였다.
But at the right moment, Jūbee and others came to save him.
그러나 그 때, 주베가 검호들을 이끌고 구하러 와 주었다.
Musashi cried, thanks to the burning friendship.
무사시는 뜨거운 우정에 울고 말았다.
But the road to becoming the number one of Jipangu has no end.
그러나 지팡구 제일의 길은 멀다.
Which road of fate should Musashi take?
사내 무사시의 숙명의 길은 어느 방향인가?
Hundred Matches
무사시, 꿈의 백번승부
In the spirit of new year's holidays, snow was covering the streets of Edotopia.
정월 기분에서 벗어나지 못한 에도토피아의 거리에 눈이 내렸다.
Meanwhile, Musashi was playing cards with Senhime and Kojirō in Edo castle, having a day to go for a journey.
그 쯤 무사시는 내일부터의 여행을 앞두고 에도 성에서 센히메, 코지로하고 카드놀이를 하고 있었다.
"Watching far away from the coast (of Tago)..." (*...it is snowing on the tall and white Fuji peaks.)
다고 해안에 나가 멀리 바라보니 (하얗게 솟은) (*후지산 봉우리에 눈이 내리고 있네)
(4th poem of Ogura Hyakunin Isshu; lit. 100 poets and poems at Ogura)
(백인일수 4장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
"A night lost in thought longing for you (knows no end)." (*Even the tiny doorframe gap grows cold.)
그대 그리워 잠 못 이루는 밤은 (유독 길구나) (*방문의 틈새조차 야속하게 느껴지네)
(85th poem)
(백인일수 85장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
"Warm sunlight (fills a fine spring day)." (*Calm mind is not there; flowers die)
따스한 햇살 (품은 화창한 봄날) (*들뜬 마음 그대로 꽃은 지고 마는가)
(33rd poem)
(백인일수 33장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
"The shore desiring for (no changes)..." (*binds the fisherman rowing a boat, with or without a rope)
변치 않기를 바라는 이 세상 (해변의) (*어부 배저어 가는 모습 무상함이 느껴지네)
(93rd poem)
(백인일수 93장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
On a frosty night with crickets (crying), (*with clothes as my pillow I am lying)
서리 내리고 귀뚜라미 우는 밤 (차디찬) (*멍석 위 옷자락 베게삼고 홀로 누워 있는가)
(91st poem)
(백인일수 91장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
The moon (outside the window is bright) (*Snow covers the village tonight)
어스름한 (밤 새벽달이 밝구나 창밖을 보니) (*마을을 뒤덮은 새하얀 눈꽃송이)
(31st poem)
(백인일수 31장)
-Mine!
-이럇!
It's not fun anymore-dasu! I quit-dasu!
더 이상 재미없소! 난 그만두오!
And I got this much.
오, 난 이렇게나 얻었구나.
Musashi. You won't cut it as a top-class martial artist, with that kind of reaction.
무사시. 그런 반사 신경으로는 제일의 무예가가 될 수 없지.
Such child's play suits Kojirō perfectly-dasu!
이런 얘들 장난은 코지로한테 딱 어울리오!
What?!
뭐라?!
Calm down, Musashi! It's the first day of the year; chill out.
자, 자, 무사시! 설날이니까 그렇게 화내지 마.
Goodness. Why can't you two get along?
정말, 왜 너희 둘은 그렇게 사이가 나쁜 거야?
I hated Kojirō ever since I met him for the first time-dasu!
코지로 따위, 처음 만났을 때부터 정말 싫었소!
Back in the day that I bid farewell to Otsuru and went on a journey of training...
오츠루하고 갈라져 수행길을 떠난 그 날.
Wait a moment-dasu!
잠, 잠깐 기다리시오!
Are you talking to me?
기다리라는 건 나 말인가.
I'd like you to be my opponent-dasu.
상대가 되어 주길 부탁드리오.
You have rice stuck to your face.
얼굴에 밥풀이나 붙이고 다니는 주제에 무슨 소리를.
Kiddo, you'd better take a nap after a lunch.
얘야, 식사 후에는 낮잠 자는 게 좋다.
I'm not a kiddo-dasu!
꼬마 따위 아니오!
I'll cut it short. You should go back and help with fieldworks.
나쁜 소리는 하지 않겠다. 마을에 돌아가서 밭일이나 도와줘라.
Damn you, don't look down on me-dasu!
네이놈, 업신여기지 마시오!
It's cowardly to jump up-dasu!
뛰어 올라가다니 비겁하오!
And attacking from behind isn't?
뒤에서 달려드는 것은 비겁한 것이 아니냐!
Stop complaining so that we can settle this right here right now-dasu! Come-dasu!
잡소리 말고 바로 승부를 내오! 자, 오시오!
Sure! I'll show you how relentless is the path of martial arts!
좋다! 무예의 길이란 얼마나 혹독한 것인지 알려 주겠다!
Here I come!
무사시 등장!
Secret Sword Tsubamegaeshi!
비검! 츠바메가에시!
Farewell, Musashi. Idiot.
안녕이다, 무사시. 바보 녀석.
Hey! The match isn't...
야! 승부는 아직...
No way...
말도 안 돼...
Thinking about it makes me furious-dasu!
생각하면 또 속이 뒤집어지오!
But Musashi, you did become stronger compared to that time before!
그래도 무사시, 그 때에 비해서 꽤나 강해지지 않았니?
That's obvious-dasu!
당연하오!
I was trained under my master Bokuden, with my life at stake-dasu!
나, 보쿠덴 스승님에게 목숨을 걸고 수련받았소!
It was pretty bitter-dasu...
꽤나 쓰라렸지만...
Soft and naive!
무디다! 무뎌!
Master!
스승님!
What are you doing-dasu?!
뭔 짓이오!
You idiot! Do you think your opponent is going to save you in real battles?
바보 녀석! 실제 싸움에서 구해주는 놈이 있을 거라 생각하나!
He was a fine guy, to keep onto his sword to his death.
괜찮은 사내었다... 죽을 때까지 검을 놓지 않다니.
Chink in the armor!
빈틈이오!
I wonder how fares Master Bokuden nowadays-dasu.
보쿠덴 스승님, 요즘 어떻게 지내시려나...
Musashi?
무사시?
Yes, what is it-dasu?
예, 무엇이오?
You told me that you went to train yourself after bidding farewell to Otsuru, right?
아까 오츠루하고 갈라져 수행길을 떠났다고 했잖아?
Who is Otsuru?
오츠루는 누구야?
Could she be Musashi's lover?
설마 무사시의 애인인가?
Hey, Musashi isn't to be underestimated, I guess!
어라, 무사시도 가볍게는 못 보겠는걸?
You embarrass me-dasu!
그러면 곤란하오!
That day, I was scolded by the monk Takuan,
그 날, 타쿠안 스님에게 혼나서
but Otsuru saved me, hanging down from a tree-dasu!
나무에 매달려진 날 오츠루가 구해주었소!
It's all right now!
이제 괜찮네요!
But Otsuru, you're going to be scolded-dasu!
그래도 오츠루 씨 혼나겠소!
No, don't worry about it. I was happy to see you with those sparrows!
아니에요, 걱정하지 말고 전 무사시 씨가 참새하고 같이 있는 걸 보고 정말 기뻤어요!
You really have a kind spirit inside of you!
그러니까 무사시 씨 사실은 정말 마음이 착한 걸 알겠어요!
You're making me blush-dasu...
수줍소...
Musashi?
무사시 씨?
What is it?
뭐오?
I made some rice balls for you.
이거 주먹밥이에요.
Otsuru!
오츠루 씨!
I hope that Master will understand.
스님도 알아주실 거에요.
Agreed.
그러오.
Musashi ran away!
무사시가 도망쳤다!
-Hurry up, Mr. Musashi! -Right!
-자, 무사시 씨, 빨리! -알겠소.
Follow your dreams.
꼭 꿈을 이루세요!
Thank you. I will definitely become the number one martial artist of Jipangu-dasu!
고맙소. 난 꼭 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되겠소!
Otsuru, I... I...
오츠루 씨, 저... 저...
Yes, what is it?
네, 뭐에요?
I... I'd like a farewell from you-dasu!
저... 작별인사를 해 주면 고맙겠소!
Stay well, Musashi!
건강하세요, 무사시 씨!
I decided that day-dasu. I'll invite Otsuru to become my wife when I become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
나, 그 날 정했소. 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 된다면 오츠루를 부인으로 맞이하겠다고!
Otsuru...
오츠루...
So, Musashi...
그래서 무사시.
Will Otsuru remain as a bachelorette until you become the best of Jipangu?
오츠루, 네가 지팡구 제일이 될 때까지 쭉 독신이 되는 거야?
I... I guess so-dasu.
그, 그렇게 되는 것이겠소.
Too bad for Otsuru. She'll become a granny!
오츠루도 불쌍하네. 그렇게는 할머니가 되어버리겠어.
That won't happen-dasu!
그건 곤란하오!
I see-dasu. I do not have time to be playing like this-dasu!
그렇소. 나, 이런 곳에서 놀고 있을 틈 따위 없소!
What a noisy brat.
시끄러운 놈.
But you know, it sounds like Otsuru would be happy.
그래도 오츠루는 행복하겠네.
Right.
그래요.
Thanks to the winter warmer than the usual, the snow has stopped before they knew it.
조금 전만 해도 내리던 눈은 평년보다 따뜻한 겨울 때문에 어느새 그쳤다.
I'm Musashi from Miyamoto village-dasu!
미야모토 마을의 무사시이오!
I want to see Jūbee-dasu!
주베 님을 뵙고 싶소!
Welcome, Musashi.
환영합니다, 무사시 님.
What made you find me this late?
그래도 이런 시간에 어쩐 일이십니까?
I want to defeat you, Jūbee-dasu. I ask you to be my opponent-dasu!
나, 주베 씨를 이기고 싶소. 상대해 주시기를 부탁드리오!
This also is like you, Musashi.
이것 역시 무사시 님답군요.
Please, sit down, and let's talk.
일단 앉아서 이야기를 해 보죠.
Musashi. Do martial artists work on their martial art skills and skills only?
무사시 님. 무예가라는 것은 무예만을 닦는 자일까요?
We call them martial artist after all-dasu, Working on skills stands as the top priority-dasu.
그러니까, 무예가라고 하니까, 역시 무예를 닦는 것이 제일이오.
You will need tactics and strategies in battles.
싸움이라는 것에는 전술, 전략이라는 것이 필요.
In other words, you should study strategies from books to become a top martial artist.
곧, 병법서를 공부하는 것이 제일의 무예가의 길.
I am bad at reading books-dasu.
나, 책을 잘 읽지 못하오.
I like comics, thought-dasu.
만화는 좋소만.
Thankfully, reading books isn't the only way to study.
뭐든 책을 읽는 것만이 공부인 것은 아닙니다.
Are there other ways to study-dasu?
그 외에, 공부할 방법이 있소?
I'd like the simplest one-dasu.
나, 가능한 한 간단한 게 좋소.
The one that will just work!
쫌만 하면 팍 되는 놈으로.
That isn't possible.
그런 건 없습니다.
Thought so-dasu...
역시이오...
To begin, you can learn from your rivals.
일단은 라이벌에게서 배우는 것입니다.
From rivals-dasu?
라이벌이오?
You will understand once you think about the martial artists you've met so far.
무사시 님이 지금까지 만난 무예가를 생각해 보신다면 알 수 있습니다.
The martial artists I met...
내가 만난 무예가...
During my journey of training, I faced Benkei at Miyako Palace.
수행길을 떠난 나는 미야코 궁전에서 벤케이를 만났소.
You came out, Benkei! Musashi will face you-dasu!
나오셨소, 벤케이! 무사시가 상대해 주겠소!
Got it? Let's have a match to death-dasu!
알겠소? 전력으로 승부를 보겠소!
Give it up and shoo! Today is the monumental night for the 1000th.
관둬라, 관둬! 오늘밤은 기념할 만한 천인째의 밤.
I decided the opponent to be an important person.
그 상대는 실력있는 거물로 정했다.
Now, get lost, kid!
자! 얘야! 얼렁 비켜라!
Shut up! I am not a kid! I am the only student of Bokuden, the master swordsman!
닥치시오! 난 아이가 아니오! 검성 보쿠덴의 가르침을 받은 제일의 제자이오!
What a noisy kid!
시끄러운 애새끼가!
I bought this sword today and...
산 지 얼마 안 된 칼이...
I see it's settled. Game over.
벌써 여기까지군. 게임 오버다.
Boil me or set me on fire; do whatever you want-dasu!
이렇게 됐으면 삶든 태우든 맘대로 하시오!
Don't interfere! Just get lost!
방해하지 마라! 얼렁 비켜라!
That moment, that Ushiwaka appeared-dasu.
그 때, 그 우시와카가 나타났소.
Stop.
멈춰라.
What is it?
뭔가?
I will take what you have on your waist.
그 허리에 있는 것을 가져가겠다.
Oh? This?
오? 이걸?
Your gold large war sword will be a perfect fit for the 1000th item of my collection.
그쪽의 금 야태도, 참으로 나의 천 번째로 어울리는 것.
Wouldn't you obediently pass it over?
순순히 주지 않겠는가?
No way.
싫다.
If then... I'll simply take it myself!
그렇다면... 얻어서 내 것으로 만들 때까지!
You bastard!
이놈!
I'll get rid of the scoundrel that rampages in Miyako!
미야코를 휩쓰는 고얀놈, 내가 퇴치하겠다!
What?!
뭐시라?!
Don't make me laugh!
놀리지 마라!
Any problems?
뭔 일이냐?
Dammit... How impudent!
젠장... 시건방진 것!
What?!
뭐야?!
How's that? Can you stand up to me?
어떤가. 내게 당해 낼 수 있겠는가?
That's nothing.
뭔 이까짓 걸로...
I lost, as you see.
져, 졌다. 제가 졌습니다.
I do not need such a useless thing. You shall train more.
필요 없는 장물이다. 더욱 수련해야겠구나.
Please wait! Tell me your name!
기, 기다려 주십시오! 일단 존함을!
I am Ushiwaka. You may call me Ushiwaka.
나는 우시와카. 우시와카라 하오.
Ushiwaka... Please wait!
우시와카 님... 기, 기다려 주십시오!
Please! I beg of you! Have Benkei!
제발! 부디! 벤케이를!
That moment, I learned that there is always someone better than me-dasu.
나, 그 때, 위에는 위가 있다는 것을 깨달았소.
They say that the god does not give two gifts-dasu, but...
하늘은 공평하다고 하지만...
Not only Ushiwaka is handsome, but he's also strong, and that's unfair-dasu!
우시와카 씨는 미남에, 게다가 강하기까지 하니 앙큼하오!
Musashi, you're a pretty good man too.
무사시 님도 꽤 하는 남자랍니다.
Really-dasu?!
정말이오?
I knew it!
역시!
This is no time to be shy, Musashi! Wait for the stormy latter half!
수줍어하고 있을 때냐, 무사시! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
There was no end to Musashi and Jūbee's conversation on martial arts deep into night.
무사시와 주베의 무예담은 밤이 깊어져도 계속될 뿐이었다.
And we met Hōzōin when we were journeying together.
그리고 저와 같이 있을 때 만난 자가 호조인 님.
That person was strong too-dasu!
그 사람도 강했소!
I want to have a match against Hōzōin-dasu!
다음은 호조인 님과 승부를 보고 싶소!
Some confidence you have, to hold your sword against me. Well then.
칼을 내게 세우다니, 배짱 좋구나. 좋다.
But I do not have a match without a real sword. Will you accept?
다만 진검승부 이외에는 하지 않겠다. 괜찮나?
That's what I wanted-dasu!
바라던 바이오!
That's one strange lance-dasu!
희한한 창이오!
(kamayari: 鎌槍. Spear with curved cross-blades)
이 미늘창이야말로 우리 호조인류의 필살무기!
Begin match!
승부다!
I didn't put the metal part to my calculations-dasu...
쇠붙이 부분을 계산에 넣지 않았소.
Did you see? This is the specialty of kamayari of our Hōzōin family. This spear also can cut. It is capable of anything.
보았나? 이게 호조인류 미늘창의 특기. 그것뿐만이 아니라 자르는 기능도 있는 만능 창.
Prepare yourself!
각오해라!
I cannot find a way to take advantage of anything-dasu!
이대로는 허점을 이용할 틈이 전혀 없소!
Finishing move!
끝장이다!
Are you running away, you brat?!
달아가냐, 꼬맹아!
That's not it! I just came out because the air was stale inside that limited space of Dōjō!
아니오! 좁은 도장에서는 숨이 막히니까 밖으로 나왔을 뿐이오!
One second before you admit your loss!
패배를 인정하기 1초 전이군!
I cannot move-dasu!
움직일 수가 없소!
Time for skewering!
이랴, 꼬치 꽂기다!
Prepare yourself!
각오해라!
Who did that?!
누구냐!
How dare you...
네이놈.
Huh? You're...
어? 너는...
The opponent is a boy. If you must fight, I will content with you.
상대는 아직 소년. 굳이 날뛰어야 한다면 소생이 상대하겠습니다.
Emblem of hollyhock. He must be Jūbee, director of the police department who takes care of whole empire...
접시꽃 문장. 제국을 돌아보는 경찰청 장관 주베 님인가...
Did you forget the match-dasu, Hōzōin? Prepare yourself!
승부를 잊었소, 호조인? 각오하시오!
I lost.
졌소.
Why-dasu? This match is a draw...
어째서오? 지금 승부는 비긴 것이...
No. It is my loss, as my spear has been cut off, as well as my pride.
아니오. 자랑스러운 창이 끊어진 제가 진 것이오.
I will devote more, from now on.
이후, 정진하겠소이다.
Re- really?
저, 정말이오?
I did it! I did it-dasu!
해냈다! 해냈소!
Musashi, you were strong too back then.
그 때의 무사시 님도 강했지요.
But it's all thanks to you-dasu, Jūbee!
그래도 주베 씨 덕이오!
And Baiken, the yielder of Kusarigama.
그리고 쿠사리가마를 쓰는 바이켄 님.
I never saw a weapon like that before then-dasu!
그런 무기, 나 그 때 처음 봤소!
No!
저런!
I lost.
내가 졌다.
After that match, we became friends-dasu.
이 승부 후 우리 사이 좋아졌소.
Friendship born of rivalry.
라이벌을 넘은 우정이란 것이겠소.
What is this sound?
이 소리는?
My stomach just rang-dasu. I'm hungry...
내 배가 울렸소. 배고파져서...
Alright. I'll get you a meal.
알겠습니다. 식사를 준비해 드리지요.
It's so good-dasu!
맛있소!
By the way, Musashi. Can you pick one of those beans with one chopstick?
그런데 무사시 님. 그 콩을 젓가락 하나로 집을 수 있을까요?
Huh? Using only one?
어? 하나로?
It's impossible with only one chopstick-dasu!
젓가락 하나로는 무리이오.
Then, how is it using two?
그럼 둘이라면 어떻습니까.
This is easy-dasu.
이거라면 쉽소.
That's how it is.
그런 것입니다.
That's how it is?
그런 것?
Kojirō may have a secret sword named Tsubamegaeshi, but only one sword is used.
코지로 님에게 츠바메가에시라는 비검이 있다고 해도, 그 칼은 하나.
You have two swords!
칼은 둘이 있다!
Dual blade...
이도류...
You have showed me the technique of using dual blades before.
언젠가 우연히 보여주신 이도류의 기술.
If you explore further...
그걸 공부한다면...
Dual blade...
이도류...
From the extra match between Musashi and Jūbee in the martial arts competition...
무예 대회에서의 무사시와 주베의 번외 시합.
Start!
시작!
No! I'll be done for at this rate-dasu! I need something!
안 돼! 이대로는 당하오! 이대로는!
Is there a way to get over-dasu?
어떻게 타개할 방법은 없소?
What he showed us back then is the technique of dual blades.
그 때, 우연히 보여준 것이 이도류였다.
If you build upon that posture, you might become the matchless martial artist as well.
그 자세를 공부한다면 천하무적의 무예가가 될 지도 모릅니다.
So I should study dual blades-dasu!
이도류를 공부하는 것이겠소!
I suggest you to develop your technique of dual blades to perfection on the journey with Kojirō.
코지로 님과 함께 여행하면서 자신의 검술을 수련하며 이도류를 완성하는 건 어떨지요.
Understood-dasu. I will take Kojirō down by studying the technique of dual blade-dasu!
알겠소. 나, 꼭 이도류를 공부해서 숙명의 라이벌, 코지로를 쓰러뜨리겠소!
Once you develop the technique of dual blade, you will eliminate these monsters.
이도류를 완성한 새벽녘에는 이 괴물을 퇴치하십시오.
Yamata no Orochi?
야마타노오로치?
Tsuchigumo?
츠치구모?
They are monsters that are told to be protecting the sacred swords named Tenkūmaru and Tenchimaru.
신이 다스리던 시대부터 명도 천공환, 천지환을 지키고 있다고 전해지는 괴물입니다.
So by getting rid of those monsters, I will claim those excellent swords-dasu!
그 괴물을 퇴치하면 그 명도가 손에 들어오는 것이오!
When that time comes, Musashi, you'll become the best of the best swordsmen around the world.
그 때야말로 무사시 님은 천하제일의 검호가 되겠죠.
Thank you so much-dasu, Jūbee!
주베 씨, 감사하오!
I'll do that with all my might!
나, 힘껏 해 보겠소!
This is the hint to Musashi's realization of Niten'ichiryū,
이것이 바로 무사시의 이천일류 개안의 힌트가 되긴 했지만
but Musashi will probably forget soon as his tummy is full.
배가 불룩해져서 바로 잊어먹을 결정을 한 무사시.
Will the goddess of fate smile at him?
과연 숙명의 여신은 미소를 지어 줄까?
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
To guard Senhime and develop the technique of dual blade, we headed to the east first-dasu.
센히메 방위와 이도류 수행길에 떠난 우리 셋은 일단 동쪽으로 향했소.
When we were at an eerie swamp,
섬뜩한 늪에 다가갔을 때,
a strange Karakuri martial artist yielding a giant toad has appeared-dasu.
말도 안 되게 거대한 두꺼비를 조종하는 이상한 카라쿠리 무예가가 나타났소.
The name of that guy is Jiraiyan, one of the Four Rulers of Iga!
그 자의 정체는 이하 사천왕의 하나, 지라이얀!
Next story! Giant Toad Magic, Jiraiyan-dasu!
다음 이야기! 거대 두꺼비 요술 지라이얀이오!
It'll be a stormy journey-dasu!
질풍노도의 여행이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Giant Toad Magic
거대 두꺼비 요술 지라이얀
Jiraiyan
기대하세요!